ILGWU. Gus Tyler papers, 5780/052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Articles., 1950-1980
  - Riots, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Encyclopedia International, February 1967.
  - Riots: A Cool View of A Hot Summer, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Mademoiselle, June 1968.
  - The Riots of Organized Crime, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Reprint, Crime and Delinquency, October 1962, pp. 325-338.
  - Scarcity: A Critique Of The American Economy, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Book distribution, author questionnaire by Quadrangle/N.Y. Times Boole Co.
  - SERD/Human Development Institute, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    G.T. critique of SERD/HDI Report On The Community and Citizen Mobilization Programs conducted by the National Council on Crime and Delinquency and the AFL-CIO Community Service Committee.
  - Seventy-Two Is Critical Year For Politics, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Northeast News, December 1971.
  - Shoes, Textiles, Specialty Steel (The Story Behind Those Cheap Imports), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Beaver County (Pa.) Times. May 20, 1977.
  - Sociodynamics of Organized Crime", 1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Symposium at Emory University, Atlanta Georgia on Organized Crime, Journal of Public Law. Vol. 20, No. 1, March 1971.
  - Strategy for Labor, by Andre Gorz. Book review, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    May 1967.
  - Toward A Democratic Left, by Michael Harrington, Book review, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    June 1968
  - The Truth About The ILGWU. A Refutation of Herbert Hill's article "The ILGWU Today-The Decay of A Labor Union" (also included), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    New politics. Vol II, No. 1, Fall 1962.
  - Unions and Politics in The United States, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sen. Robert F. Wagner and The Rise of Urban Liberalism, by Joseph Hutmacher, Book review, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    December 1968.
  - We shall Be All: A History of The Industrial Workers Of The World, by Melvin Dubofsky Book Review, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    September 1969.
  - What The Nixon Budget Means, The Enquirer. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Who Shall Serve?-(The Problem of Military Manpower), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    The Call. July 1967
  - Why Has Socialism Failed To Take Root With The American Working Class? (Box 34, Folder 12)
    G.T. comment in Failure of a Dream? Essays in the History of American Socialism, edited by John h. M. Laslett and Seymour Martin Lipset
  - Why They Organise, by Felix Nigro, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    October 1971
  - Women And The American Labor Movement: From Colonial Times to the Eve of World War I, by Philip S. Foner. Book review, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    December 1979.
  - Women Tied To Low Pay In Occupational Ghettos, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Democratic Left, September 1980,
  - Your Union Reports - Radio Campaign for a Union Addresses prepared and delivered by G.T. for the ILGWU, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Articles, Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Incl. G.T. articles on redistricting "Reapportionment 1972 The Salami Slicing" and "Work Not A Four-Letter Word".
  - Articles, Miscellaneous. Untitled, Undated. (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Syndicated column, 1974-1980
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 1-75 (1-29 missing), 1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    June 13, 1974.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate, No, 76-149, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    June 20-December 5, 1974.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 150-225, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    December 7, 1974-May 31, 1975.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 226-300, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    June 3, 1975-Hovember 20, 1975.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate, Ho. 301-375, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    November 22, 1975-May 15, 1976.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate, No. 376-450, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    May 8, 1976-November 4, 1976.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 451-525, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    November 12, 1976-April 28, 1977.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 526-599, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    April 29, 1977-October 18, 1977.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No, 601-675, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    October 28, 1977 -April 27, 1978.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No, 676-750, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    April 28, 1978-October 19, 1978.
  - Syndicated Column. United Feature Syndicate. No. 751-832, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    October 20; 1978-April 30, 1979.
  - Syndicated Column. (independent), 1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    May 2, 1979- December 1979.
  - Syndicated Column. (independent), (1979)1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Series V. General correspondence, 1963-1975
  - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    January 1970-February 1970,
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    March 1970-Becember 1970,
  - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Series VI. Subject files., 1950-1975
  - A, 1963-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - The Academy for Contemporary Problems, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - The Academy for Contemporary Problems, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Germany, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1963-1965 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO, 1963-1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO, 1963-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO, COPE, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO, COPE, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO, COPE, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO, Education Department, 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO, Labor College, 1970-1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO, National Convention, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State Convention, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - American National Exhibition in Moscow, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - ASPIRA, 1963-1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - B, 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Beame, Abraham, Political Campaign for Mayor of New York City [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Incl. material issued by Campaign Committee, and letter from Paul O'Dwyer requesting endorsement of his candidacy for City Council President.
  - Beame, Abraham, Political Campaign for Mayor of New York City [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Corres. re. Mrs. Beatrice Nebel's request for transfer of teaching assignment.
  - Bodden, Mark, 1970-1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Brookings Institution, 1969-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Burke-Hartke Trade Bill, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Burke-Hartke Trade Bill, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - C, 1960-1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Incl. "Corruption in Trade Unions" by Tyler in Yale Political, May 1963.
  - California, University of at Berkeley, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Corres. re. Minority Union Leadership Training Program.
  - Campaigns, Political, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Campaigns, Political, Goldberg-Pattersons, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Campaigns, Political, 1971-1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Center for Migration Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Conference on " Labor and the Migrant".
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1963-1970 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Incl. Corres. w. Robert M. Hutchins, Chairman.
  - Central States Region, 1963-1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Incl. Corres. w. Frederick Siems.
  - Central States Region, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Central States Region, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - The Citizens' Commission on the Future of the City University of Hew York, 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Cloak Joint Board and Cloak-Out-Of-Town Department, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Clothing Industry Economic Development Committee (Clothing EDC), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Corres. re visit of British Clothing EDC study group.
  - Columbia University, 1970-1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Congress, U.S. [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Congress, U.S. [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Consumer Federation of America, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Corres. w. Evelyn Dubrow.
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Corres. re Discussion Study Group on the Changing Domestic Base of U.S. Foreign Policy.
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Incl. Corres. re Corporate Consultation Program.
  - D, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Party, 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Incl. Corres. w. the Democratic National Committee and its Democratic Policy Council, This includes corres. between Hubert H. Humphrey and Louis Stulberg.
  - Democratic Party, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Incl. Corres. w. Democratic Party Charter Commission.
  - Democratic Party, 1972-1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Incl. Corres. w. the Democratic National Committee and its Democratic Policy Council, copies of the Democratic Letter, corres. w. the Democratic Study Group.
  - Dubinsky, David, 1947-1964 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Dubinsky David, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    August 1965.
  - Dubinsky, David, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    May 1966.
  - Dubinsky, David, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    February 1970-January 1971.
  - Dubinsky-Stulberg Dinner, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    June 14, 1966.
  - David Dubinsky article, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    New York Times. May 17, 1959.
  - E, 1973-1976 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - The Edward Corsi Labor-Management Relations Institute of Pace College, 1972-1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Region, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Education Department, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Education Department, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Education Department, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Incl. local newsletters.
  - El Diario, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Corres. w. Stanley Ross, editor.
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Incl. ILGWU campaign literature for Abraham Beame campaign for Mayor of New York City. Also includes analysis of City and State elections throughout nation.
  - Encampment for Citizenship, 1968-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - F, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Incl. material on White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health, December 1969, corres. between Donald L. Foucer, Chairman, Democratic Party of South Carolina and Evelyn Dubrow.
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1964-1971 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, Urban Affairs Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Form Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Frontlash, 1968-1972 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Frontlash, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - G, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Garment Industry, Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1963 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Garment Industry, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - General Executive Board, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    December 1944.
  - General Executive Board, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    June 1957.
  - General Executive Board [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    May 1958.
  - General Executive Board [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - General Executive Board, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    November 1958.
  - General Executive Board, 1958-1959 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    November 1958 and April 1959.
  - General Executive Board, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    April 1959.
  - General Executive Board, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    August 1959.
  - General Executive Board, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    January 1960.
  - General Executive Board, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    August 1960.
  - General Executive Board, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    January-February 1961.
  - General Executive Board, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    May 1961.
  - General Executive Board, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    November 1961.
  - General Executive Board, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    April 1962.
  - General Executive Board, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    September 1962.
  - General Executive Board, 1963-1965 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - General Executive Board, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - General Executive Board, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    January 1969.
  - General Executive Board, 1970-1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - General Executive Board (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Undated.
  - General Executive Board, New York Board, 1944-1954 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - General Executive Board, New York Board, 1957-1962 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Grassroots, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Consumer action organization opposing New York Telephone Company rate hike.
  - H, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Hampshire College, 1968-1970 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee of the AFL-CIO, 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Hoffman, S.L., 1970-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Housing, Union Sponsored, 1959-1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Hudson Guild, 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Hudson institute, 1964-1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., Political Campaign, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - I, 1967-1973 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - The Institute for the Future, 1967-1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda [folder 1 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda [folder 2 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - J, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Conciliation Board of America, Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1963-1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Justice, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - K, 1964-1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Incl. material from Estes Kefauver Memorial Foundation.
  - L, 1962-1974 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Incl. ILGWU quarterly lobbying reports to House of Representatives for 1973 and Tyler article "Liberal or Conservative" in Liberal News, Spring 1972. taken from speech given to Young Republicans.
  - Labor Education, ILGWU, 1964-1971 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    ILGWU labor education program in Wyoming Valley, PA.
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Incl. draft of Tyler speech for presentation of award to Hubert H. Humphrey.
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1970-1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Liberal Party, 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Incl. Robert F. Kennedy corres.
  - M, 1967-1973 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Management Engineerings, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript. History of ILGWU and Puerto Rican workers in the Union. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    No Author. Undated.
  - McGovern, George, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - The Medgar Evers Fund, 1969-1972 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Midwest Department, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Minimum Wage [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Incl. Wilbur Daniels statement re Amendments to the Pair Labor Standards Act before the Subcommittee on Labor, 1971.
  - Minimum Wage [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1969 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Education, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Incl. material on scholarships and education programs of Boston Joint Board and Northern New England District Council.
  - N [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Incl. Corres. re National Center for Education in Politics, Tyler address to National Municipal League and League of Women Voters, April 20, 1972.
  - N [folder 2 of 2], 1958-1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - National Center for Education in Politics [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - National Center for Education in Politics [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - The National Industrial Conference Board, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - National Institute of Labor Education [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1971 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Labor Education [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1971 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - National Recreation Association, 1963-1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - New America, 1969-1971 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - The New Republic [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1963 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Incl. Tyler articles and letter from Humbert H. Humphrey, November 26, 1957.
  - The New Republic [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1963 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - The New Republic, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Corres. re Tyler article "Save the Electoral College".
  - The New Republic, 1960-1962 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Draft of 1960 Tyler article on the Electoral College and "Prescription for Representation" 1962. June 1962 by Tyler.
  - New School for Social Research, 1955-1963 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Incl. Corres. re Tyler manuscript Our Representative Government, 1955-57, and Tyler course on organized crime.
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - New York City, 1963-1973 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Incl. Corres. re political campaigns.
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1962-1972 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - New York City, city Planning Commission, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - New York City Democratic Committee, Inc., 1971 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - New York Dressmakers' Joint Board, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Mew York Locals, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    Incl. decision of Impartial Chairman in case of Local 102 and Julian Schiff, #6320, vs. Moledzky Transportation Corp. 1964. November 1964, corres. re members' complaints, locals' recruitment and training of personnel, scholarship fund.
  - New York Local Managers Meetings, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    September 14, 1950.
  - New York Post, 1957-1959 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Incl. Corres. w. Dorothy Schiff.
  - New York State Democratic Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - New York State Governor's Commission to Review New York Laws and Procedures in the Area of Human Rights [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - New York State Governor's Commission to Review New York Laws and Procedures in the Area of Human Rights [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - New York University School of Law, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Incl. Tyler speech "The Role of Trade Unions in a Democratic Society", presented at the 14th Annual Conference on Labor, May 1961.
  - Northeast Department, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Notre Dame Law School, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Incl. Corres. re Symposium on Labor Union Power and the Public Interest.
  - O, 1960-1962 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Office Managers' Forum for New York City Area, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Proposal and corres. re establishment of such a forum.
  - Ohio-Kentucky Regions, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Incl. article on minimum wage, no author.
  - The Open Mind Television Program, 1959-1963 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Incl. transcript of program "Do We Need a New Look at Labor?", January 1963.
  - P, 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Panel of Americans, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    A nationwide discussion program in intergroup education.
  - Peace Corps, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Peace Research Institutes, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    Incl. Tyler paper "The Next Twenty Years - A Positive View", 1963.
  - Pins and Needles, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Corres. re proposed production of Pins and Needles.
  - Politea, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Politea, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Politea [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    December 1970- August 1971.
  - Politea [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Politea [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    September 1971-December 1971.
  - Politea [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Politea [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    January 1972-May 1972.
  - Politea [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    June 1972-July 1972.
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    August 1972-December 1972.
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Politea, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Political Department, 1959-1965 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Incl. Corres. w. members of Congress.
  - Political Department, 1965-1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Political Department, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Politics, U.S.A., 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Progressive Magazine, 1959-1962 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Incl. Tyler's review of Unions and Union Leadership by Jack Barbash.
  - Protestant Board of Guardians, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Puerto Rican Organizations, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Puerto Rico Region, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Puerto Rico Regions, 1966-1973 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - R, 1957-1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Radio Station WBAI, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Incl. Corres. re Tyler broadcasts.
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1967-1972 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - The Role of Trade Unions in a Democratic Society, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Tyler article.
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers University, 1957-1963 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Ryan, William Fitz, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - S, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - S, 1963-1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - St. John's College, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Incl. Corres. re Tyler meeting with foreign trade unionists.
  - Save the Electoral College, 1960 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    Tyler article reprinted from the New Republic, November 1960.
  - Senate, U.S., 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Settlement Housing Fund, Inc., United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Silva, Ruth C., 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    Incl. Corres. re reapportionment.
  - Socialist Party, 1962-1963 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Southeast Region, 1963-1965 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Southeast Region, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Southeast Region, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Incl. Corres. re A. Philip Randolph Institute conferences.
  - South Jersey-Philadelphia, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Staff Orientation Institute, N.Y.C., 1972 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    November 1972- December 1972. Institute taught staff about the I.L.G.W.U.
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    The Port Huron Statement of the Students for a Democratic Society.
  - Stulberg, Judith, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - T, 1961-1973 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Toward Party Realignment, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Tyler article in New Politics. Winter 1962.
  - Training Institute, I.L.G.W.U., 1958-1965 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Tulane University, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Incl. Tyler article "The Proper Function of Unions"; 1960.
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 11)